wewanttraffic.com 2016-04-16

# Traffic Website Privacy and Security Statement

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Traffic Group. Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy. In order to obtain more information about our products and services, it is the policy of Traffic Group. Ltd that personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is private and confidential. Because your privacy is important to us, Traffic Group. Ltd maintains privacy policies to protect your personal information. We may use your personal information to market third party products and services to you. However, we shall obtain your permission prior to providing your details to such third parties and every time we email you for third party marketing purposes we will give you the chance to refuse any such emails in the future. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

Traffic Group. Ltd automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Traffic Group. Ltd cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. Traffic Group. Ltd uses this information for the following general purposes: - to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal use.

Read more

## Website Privacy Policy

By using this site, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your consent or as required by law.

Read more

## How long will the Traffic keep my personal information?

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant service, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with Traffic Group. Ltd or Traffic Group. Ltd corporate retention schedule (this is a database that defines which documents should be kept and for how long). In the case that you wish to cancel your account services with Traffic Group. Ltd, once an account is deleted a red flag goes on the database and, while people cannot use the personal information, it stays on the system for a period of one year for administration purposes before being deleted automatically.

Where you contribute content to Traffic Group. Ltd we will generally only keep your content for as long as is reasonably required for the purpose(s) for which it was submitted.

Traffic Group. Ltd does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Traffic Group. Ltd under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Traffic Group. Ltd deliver enhanced services communicate with you about new products or services from Traffic Group. Ltd. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Traffic Group. Ltd terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if Traffic Group. Ltd is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Traffic Group. Ltd will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Traffic Group. Ltd will on occasion display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Traffic Group. Ltd advertisers may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteriafor example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

Traffic Group. Ltd does not provide any personal information to any advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

Read more

## Cookies Policy -Information Traffic collects from you

### A. What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone (referred to here as a "device") browser from a website's computer and is stored on your device's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online Traffic Group. Ltd flows.

Cookies record information about your online preferences and allow us to tailor the websites to your interests. Users have the opportunity to set their devices to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the Traffic Group. Ltd website features.

Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

During the course of any visit to the Traffic Group. Ltd website, the pages you see, along with a cookie, are downloaded to your device. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the device (and probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.

Read more

### B. How does Traffic Group. Ltd use cookies?

Information supplied by cookies can help us to analyse the profile of our visitors and help us to provide you with a better user experience. For example: if on a previous visit you went to our services pages, we might find this out from your cookie and highlight certain service information on your second and subsequent visits.

Traffic Group. Ltd also operates measurement and research trials. We gather information regarding the visitors to Traffic Group. Ltd sites on our behalf using cookies, log file data and code which is embedded on our website. Traffic Group. Ltd uses this type of information to help improve the services we provide to our users. Traffic Group. Ltd strictly require that third parties do not use any information for their own business or other purposes. Certain other areas of the Traffic Group. Ltd site may use cookies for a specific reason - for example, to help an online element work effectively on your device. If this is the case, the local terms for that area of the website will make this clear and you should refer to those local terms for additional information.

Read more

## Will I be contacted for marketing purposes?

Traffic Group. Ltd won't contact you for marketing purposes, or promote new services to you unless you specifically agree to be contacted for these purposes.

## Changes to Traffics Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may be updated from time to time so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information through any Traffic Group. Ltd website. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us via contact form.

Read more

## How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us via contact form.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Read more
